So what are y'all going to say at Miss Amanda Seals?
I am here in Mississippi, all right now in Jackson with the fabulous folks of I See Success Too.
And I really am so happy I finally get to meet y'all in person.
Basically, I saw y'all on Instagram and I just saw the stuff that y'all do with these kids.
Mama Bearhead, they're both.
What color is that?
Yellow.
What's her name?
Ruby Bridge.
And I was like, y'all, what y'all need?
Yeah, we received what we needed.
And now we finally get to meet.
It's cozy.
The world's cozy.
Is it cozy?
Come here.
Yeah.
And y'all got y'all some new, the puzzles have made.
Tell Miss Seals, thank you.
Yay.
I really want y'all to also follow I See Success Too, whether you're in Jackson or not.
But especially all my childhood educators and all my folks with kids.
Because the stuff that they do with the children really shows you that they are raising adults.
They're not raising kids.
Kids do not stay kids, y'all.
They become members of this world.
And we need to make sure that when they're in childhood education, that they are actually being not groomed, but they are being shaped into visions of their own imagination.
And that's what I love to see y'all do.
What's these, Quaderie's?
My ID.
Good job.
So you need to have these to get on the plane, right?
It's your ID, but what else is it called?
Passport.
Good job.
Passport and boarding pass.
What's your name?
Dre.
What's your real name?
Uh, Devin Van Kassel.
There you go.
What does ecstatic mean?
Happy.
What does annoying mean?
Don't get a body.
Can you show me?
Andre, what does ecstatic mean?
Be happy.
What does ecstatic mean?
Be good.
We're going to keep working with IT Success 2, and I'm going to be back down in the SIP.
That's what y'all call it, right?
Yeah.
Okay, the SIP.
IT Success.
Support a real one.